# William Santosa

San Ramon, CA 94582 | (925) 208-8791 | williamwsantosa@gmail.com | https://www.linkedin.com/in/williamsantosa https://github.com/williamsantosa

### **SUMMARY**

Second-year student with Junior standing majoring in Computer Science at University of California, Santa Cruz with the Dean's Honor throughout all of university (2020 & 2021). Has 10 years of experience in leadership including customer/personal interaction in martial arts, experienced logistical processes at Amazon Warehouse, and organized Science Olympiad at a state level. Is certified with AWS Certified Cloud Practitioner and proficient in Python, Java, C, and AWS services. Has exposure to SAP ABAP, SAP S/4 Hana Cloud solution, C++, and Linux.

### **EDUCATION**

# University of California, Santa Cruz

Santa Cruz, CA

Bachelor of Science, Computer Science, GPA: 4.00

Expected to graduate in 2023

Awards: Dean's Honor Fall 2020, Winter 2021, Spring 2021, Fall 2021

Coursework: Computer Architecture, Computer Systems, C Programming, Assembly Language, Calculus, Discrete Math, Abstractions, Linear Algebra

### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

# University of California, Santa Cruz

Santa Cruz, CA

College Nine Peer Navigator

June 2021 – Dec 2021

- Introduced freshmen to college and gave advice on how to succeed in their first year
- Held office hours for students that needed help with navigating the university or homework
- Graded and gave feedback to students' projects and classwork

Koo's Martial Arts San Ramon, CA

Instructor & Coach

July 2017 - Aug 2021

- Introduced students to the forms, techniques, and hard-working philosophy of Taekwondo
- Taught students the importance of hard-work, self-study, and discipline

# **Baskin School of Engineering at UCSC**

Online

Computer Systems & C Programming Reader

Mar 2021 – June 2021

- Helped students with problem solving and difficult concepts such as depth first search and recursion
- Graded and gave feedback to students' projects and classwork

### **CERTIFICATIONS**

Amazon Web Services Online

Amazon Certified Cloud Practitioner

Aug 2021

#### **SKILLS**

Programming Languages: Python, Java, C, Lua

Technologies: AWS, Git, MATLAB, Adobe Premiere Pro, Adobe Photoshop, Blender

Other: Windows, Linux, Markdown, JSON, English, Indonesian

# **SOFT SKILLS**

Leadership, Creativity, Flexible, Eager to learn, Problem solving